Autograph Collection 1559-1962 (bulk 1795-1920)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Autograph Collection 1559-1962 (bulk 1795-1920)
MS 393
Louis Schellback, T.W. Hanley
The collection consists mainly of handwritten letters, ca. 17th through 20th centuries by individuals in Europe and North America. Some files also include original envelopes, newspaper clippings, printed materials, or photographs.
4 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on access to this information
Historical Note
The materials in this collection were gifts to Special Collections from Louis Schellbach and T.E. Hanley, ca. 1960s.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into into three series:
Series I. Louis Schellbach Autograph Collection
Series II. Louis Schellbach Portrait Engravings
Series III. T.E. Hanley Autograph Collection
The collection consists mainly of handwritten letters, ca. 17th through 20th centuries by individuals in Europe and North America. Some files also include original envelopes, newspaper clippings, printed materials, or photographs. The autographs come from a range of individuals, including stage actors, military leaders, artists, senators, poets, theologians, religious leaders, and former presidents. Some notable names include Isaac Asimov, Jefferson Davis, Herbert Hoover, Abraham Lincoln, and Mark Twain. The portrait engravings, ca. 16th c, include actors, authors, doctors, and Europeans rulers. Notable names in this series include Thomas Jefferson, Benjamin Franklin, Napoleon Bonaparte, Dante Alighieri, and Marie Antoinette.
Ade, George, 1866-1944 -- Autographs; Asimov, Isaac, 1920 -- Autographs; Auden, W.H. (Wystan Hugh), 1907-1973 -- Autographs; Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925 -- Autographs; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 -- Autographs; Curtis, George William, 1824-1892 -- Autographs; Forbes, Henry Clinton, 1833-1903 -- Autographs; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964 -- Autographs; Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865 -- Autographs; Marlowe, Julia, 1865-1950 -- Autographs; McKenna, J. (Joseph), 1843-1926 – Autographs; McKinley, William, 1843-1901 -- Autographs; Morse, Jedidiah, 1761-1826 -- Autographs; Raglan, Fitzroy James Henry Somerset, Baron, 1788-1855 -- Autographs; Shafter, William Rufus, 1835-1906 -- Autographs; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930 -- Autographs; Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1811-1863 – Autographs; Twain, Mark, 1835-1910 -- Autographs; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924 -- Autographs; Autograph -- United States; Autograph -- Europe; Signatures (Writing)
Container List
- Series 1: Louis Schellbach Autograph Collection,1559-1962
  Alphabetical
  - Alexander, Peter (Count Romanoff), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bloomfield, Lady, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Buntline, Ned, 1874? (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Carpenter, Rev. Boyd, 1875? (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cole, Ashley W, "undated" (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Curtis, George William, 1882 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - D’Elisagary, Bernard Renau, 1695 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Demidoff, N. de, 1823 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Donnelly, John, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Donop, Count C.G.W., 1758 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Douglas, Robert K., undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ellis, Sir Henry, 1842 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ernst, Johann Hartwig (Count von Bernstorff), 1758 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Étienne, François (Comte de Rosily-Mesros), 1783 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Grenville, Lord George Nugent, 1789-1830 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Henderson, John, 1841 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hertford, Lord, 1861? (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Heumann(?), Christopher August, 1724 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Hill, Thomas, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hoffman, Friedrich, 1712 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hunt, John, D.D, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lahrbush, Frederick, 1766-1868 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lee, John, 1837 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Leighton, Frederick (and others), 1851-1877 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1865 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Littledale, Rev., 1872 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Low, Seth, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Lysons, Samuel, 1763-1879 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Marlowe, Julia, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Maury, Jean Siffrein, 1812 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - McCarren, Patrick H., 1890 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - McKenna, Joseph, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Mifflin, Jonathon, 1795 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Morse, Jedidiah, 1805 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Nicholson, John, 1780 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Noel, Rev. W., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Norton, Charles S., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Oakes, J.W, 1857 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Pauncefote, Sir Julian, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Phillips, Daniel B., 1890 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Pickersgill, Frederick, 1856 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Potter, Rev. Henry C., 1898 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Proctor, Col. John, 1789 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Raglan, Lord Fitzroy Somerset, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Read, John, 1849 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Reed, Thomas B., 1898 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Reynolds, Quentin, Jacket Charlies “21” menu (dinner in honor of QR), with photo, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Schaff, Adam, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Seeley, Elias B., undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Sherman, W.T., undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Slough, Col. Matthew, 1784 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Smith, George B., 1876 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Smith, H.S., 1862 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Smith, William H., 1868 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Stanley, Dean, Around 1893 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Stuart-Poole, Reginald, 1878 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Thompson, James, 1780 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Treadwell, George C., 1898 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Vaughan, Robert, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Vincent, Edgar, 1879 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Walker, Rob C., 1859 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Walling, George W., 1884 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Ward, Lieut. Aaron, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Wayne, Isaac, 1809 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Wellesley, Max, 1839 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Wellesley, Richard Marquess, 1840 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Welsh, Rev. D., 1844 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Wetmore, Prosper M., 1866 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - White, Edward, 1878 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Whiteside, J., undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Wilhelm, August, 1714-1731 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Wylie, R.C., 1863 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Young, John, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Anthony, Henry B., 1862 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Aurand, Peter, 1818 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Balliet, Stephen, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bancroft, Hubert Howe, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Baudin, Charles (des Ardennes), 1951 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baynard, Thomas F., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Beck, Christian Daniel, 1804 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Binney, Horace, 1834 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Black, Frank S., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Boone, Joseph, 1804 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Boyle, Lord David, 1850 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chambers, Joseph G., 1815 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cheetham, S., 1878 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Clark, Thomas M., 1857 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cox, Samuel, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Crosby, J. Schuyler, 1863 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cupples, George, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cushing, Marshall, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Dallas, E.S., undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Daly, James, 1884 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dennis, John, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Donaldson, James, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ebeling, Christopher Daniel, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Evarts, William M., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ewing, Alexander, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fabricius, John Albert 1710 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Farnum, Alex, 1863 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Farwell, C.B., 1887 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Fichard, Johann, 1559 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - French, Alice (Octave Thanet), 1897 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Gage, Lyman J., undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Gerstacker, Friedrich, 1867? (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Gibbons, Cardinal James, 1898 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Griggs, John W., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Hale, Rev. Edward Everett, 1885 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Hamilton, Capt. Thomas, 1781 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Hanna, Mark J., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, 1833-1901 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Harrison, Gabriel, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Hartzell, Jonas William, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1877 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hood, Edwin Paxton, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Horsley, Samuel, 1792 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Huffnagle, Michael, 1780 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Ingensoll, J.R., 1839 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ingram, John K., 1881 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Kaufman, David S., 1846 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Keteller, H., undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - MacGregor, John, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Mallock, W.H., undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - McGee, Rev. D., 1872 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - McIntosh, Col. James, 1861 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - McKean, J.B., 1809 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - McLennan, Malcolm, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Miller, Hugh, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - O’Callaghan, E.B., 1849 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Odillon-Barot, Camille Hyacinthe, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Orlando, Francisco Xavier de, 1799 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Patterson, Robert, 1803 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Picton, James Allanson, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Prose, Francis, 1790 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Raleigh, Rev. Alexander, 1872 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Reilly, John, 1884? (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Rigg, James H., 1879? (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Robinson, E., 1848 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Rogers, Henry, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Rowe, Richard, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Ross, George, 1895? (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Rylance, Rev. J.H., 1898 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Scott, Col. J.S., 1884? (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Scott, Thomas, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Siguenza y Gongora, Carlos de, normal= "1690">1690 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Swaine, Francis, 1780 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Thomson, Rev. Andrew, 1829 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Zincke, F., 1880 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Alger, Russell A., 1898 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Angelis, Jefferson de, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Breckingridge, J.C., 1898 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cook, Capt. (U.S.S. Brooklyn), 1898 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fields, Louis M., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Grant, Fred D., 1898 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hackett, James K., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hay, John, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Henderson, David B., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Herne, James A., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Irwin, May, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Long, John D., 1898 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - McKinley, William, 1897-1901 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Merritt, Gen. Wesley, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Henry, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Miller, J.N., 1899 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - O’Bradley, William, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Osborne, W.M., 1896 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Philip, John. W. Commodore, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Porter, J. Addison, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Rehan, Ada, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1898-1904 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Shafter, Major-Gen. William Rufus, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Wheeler, Gen. Joe, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Wilson, Francis, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Aitken, Mary Carlyle, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Henry, 1848 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Austin, Mary, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Badger, Rev. George Percy, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Binney, Rev. Thomas E., 1782 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Birks, Prof. T.R., 1878 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Blaikie, Prof. W.G., undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Blair, Robert, 1792 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brooks, Erastus, 1855 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Rev. Hugh S., undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brown, J. Baldwin, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Butler, Josephine E., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Butler, S., 1877 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Butt, Isaac, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Carr, J.C., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Edward, J.H. (accompanied with photograph of Secretary Shaw signing 40 million warrant for Panama Canal Purchase, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Escott, Thomas Hay Sweet, 1870 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fairbairn, Andrew Martin, 1872 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - French (?), Jared B., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - French, Bishop R.C., 1862 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Howden, Lord, 1865 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Kettell, Thomas P., 1854 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Macleod, Henry Dunning, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - McCreddy (prompter’s call for the play of Rob Roy), undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Morrison, Sir Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Nicol, Erskine, 1854 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Patterson, R.H., 1879 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Pennington, Capt. E., 1790 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Rae, John, 1880 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Simcox, Edith, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Thomas, Dylan, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Thorold, Bishop Anthony, 1872 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Wardlaw, Dr. Ralph, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Waterford, M., 1845 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Alcock, Sir Rutherford, normal= "1880">1880 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Arnoldy, J.A., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ash, Simon, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Actors and Actresses including: Barrett, Laurence; Bel Goddes, Norman; Bernhardt, Sarah; Booth, Edwin; Cushman, Charlotte; Sothern, Julia; Terry, Ellen, 1857-1932 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Boyd, A.K.H, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Britton, John, 1824 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chadwick, Capt. F.E., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Clark, J.A., 1903 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland, Grover (see also Portrait Engravings), 1894 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cotton, Ad. Charles S., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Maj. Gen. W., 1904 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dorsey, H.W., 1909 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Evans, Capt. John, 1796 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Foelker, Otto G., 1910 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Folger, Capt. William M., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fuller, Robert H., 1908 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Garvin, Lucius F.C., 1904 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Goff, John W., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Greeley, Gen. A.W., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Handy, R.B., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Higginson, Rear Ad. Frances J., undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hill, G.W., 1900-1901 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hitchcock, E.A., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hobson, Lt. Richmond Pearson, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hodge, F.W., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Irving, Henry, 1900-1903 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - La Follette, Robert M., 1907 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Langley, L.P., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Leutze, Admiral, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mack, Andrew, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Mahan, Capt. Alfred T., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - McCalla, Capt. Bowman H., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - McClure, Col. A.K., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Melba, Kellie, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Miles, Nelson A., 1898-1900 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Morgan, Sen. John T., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Morris, J.J., 1904 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Morton, Paul, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Norton, Charles Eliot, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Palmer, W.J., 1904 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Pennypacker, Sam W. Gov., >1905 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Ralston, W.R., undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Ravenel, William de C., 1910 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Root, Elihu, 1900-1911 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Sanderson, Percy, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Saunders, William, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Schley, Rear Ad. Winfield Scott, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Schoulder, James, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Taft, William H., 1909-1912 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Thackeray, William., undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Thornbury, Walter, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Twain, Mark, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Warner, Anne, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Whipple, James S., 1908 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Wildes, Capt. Frank, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1912-1914 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Wise, Capt. W.C., 1901 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Woodruff, Timothy L., 1906 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Youngs, William J., 1896-1900 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Abeles, Sigmund (w/ original etching), 1903 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Gov. C.H., 1900 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Andrews, Ad. Philip, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Will J. (see Baker and Weitzel), 1878 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Barry, Dr. (archbishop of Australia), 1876 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Bernard, Sam (w/ photograph), 1905? (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bowman, Bishop Thomas, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Bradley, Thomas J., 1897 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brooks, Maj. John R., 1900 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Abbie Farwell, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Burnham, Clara Louise, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Burroughs, John, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cabell, James Branch, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Calder, William M., 1911 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Carter, Leslie, 1898? (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Carter, Maj. Gen. W.M., 1912 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cheney, J.W. (librarian of War Dept.), 1905 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Clark, Prof. John B., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Coghlan, Capt. J.B., 1899 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Davis, H. Admiral., 1905 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Davis, H.G., 1904 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Day, William R., 1898 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Depew, Chauncey M., 1899-1903 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Drescher, John Jr., 1905 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dunn, Frances w/ signed photograph of Maxine Elliot, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fairbanks, C.W., 1904 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fielder, Gov. James, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fitch, Clyde, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fitzgerald, John J., 1911 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Goodwin, Nat C., 1900 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Graham, J.G., 1902-1903 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Graham, J.G., 1902-1903 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Harben, Will N., 1904 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Heineman, C.H., 1878 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Herrick, D. Cady, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Higgins, Gov. Frank W., 1904 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Hill, Gov. David B., 1899 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Kennedy letter (signed by ?), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lagerlof, Selma w/ photographs, 1940? (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lawton, Gen. H.L., 1898 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Lodge, H.C., 1913 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Lowell, A. Lawrence, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Maher, James P., 1912 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Mansfield, Richard, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Marshall, W.L., 1900 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Mason, William E., 1900 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Odell, Gov. B.B., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Olcott, Chauncey, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Palmer, William J., 1905 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Parker, Alton B. Judge w/ photograph, 1903-1904 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Peary, Com. Robert E., 1904 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Platt, T.C., 1898-1901 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Pugin, M.I., 1901 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Rathbun, Richard, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Roberts, George Evans? (dir. Of the mint), 1899-1900 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Sampson, Rear Ad. W.G., 1898-1899 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Schwahn, H.F.D., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Shafroth, John F., 1913 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Shaw, L.M. (sec. of treasury), 1904 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Sherman, Jacob David? (Cornell University), undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Sherman, V.P. James S., 1909 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Sherman, John, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Sigsbee, Capt. Charles D., 1900 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Skinner, Charles R., 1903 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Weaver, Mayor John, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Weitzel, Ed. W. (see Baker and Weitzel), undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Wilkie, Wendall, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Wilson, Frank E., 1900-1901 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Wingate, George W., 1914 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Wood, N.S. (actor), 1905 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Zangwill, Israel, 1899 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Subseries 1: Unidentified
    - ?, John (economist), 1838 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Archbishop of York, 1880 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Barton, W (?), 1789 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Bishop of Gloucester and Bristol, 1802 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Buider (?), 1884 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Cadwalder (?), J. (postmaster), 1870 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Gledhill, R.L.?, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Griffith, W.?, 1897 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - H., Henry, 1814 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Heister (?), Daniel Jr., 1781 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Hoar, Sen., 1904 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Howson (?), Dean, 1873 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Kurth (assemblyman), 1896 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - MacDuff (?), Rev. Dr, 1873 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Marquis of Lome, 1878 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Melborne (?), Lord, 1844 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Mousell (?), John (hymn writer), 1872 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Nixon, C.?, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - North, Col., 1782 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - R., George, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Rowan (?), 1898 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Sekyll (?), undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Vaughan, ?, 1872 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Vilmorin, H. (?), undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - W (?), Samuel (bishop of Winchester), undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Wellington, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Wescott, 1877 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Winthrop (?), Sargent, 1822 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Series 2: Louis Schellbach Portrait Engravings
  - Rare Engravings (Early type), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - “Very rare 17th and 18th Century copper plate and steel portrait engravings”, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - “Rare Engravings, Portraits of Churchmen, Military Men (also actors, authors- XIXc), and Women (xix c)”, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - “Fine Steel Portrait Engravings of Famous Statesmen, Rulers, Doctors, and Authors”, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Portrait Engravings. Selected individuals: Thomas Jefferson, Benjamin Franklin, James Madison, John Adams, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Portrait Engravings, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous portraits- includes military men, rulers, painters, etc., undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Portrait Engravings. Selected individuals: Dante Alighieri, Marie Antoinette, Joan of Arc, Napoleon Bonaparte, William Shakespeare, Louis XIV, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Portrait Engravings, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Series 3: T.E. Hanley Autograph Collection
  - Alexander, Russell George, 1867-1935 Poem entitled “Sapperton”, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Archer, William, 1856-1924, 1898-1923 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Asimov, Isaac, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Baillie, Joanna, 1762-1851, 1804 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Beaconsfield, Benjamin Disraeli, 1804-1881, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Beaconsfield, Benjamin Disraeli, 1804-1881, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Boettger, Rudolph, 1874? (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Bolles, Frederick, 1938-1952 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Boule-Mineo, Margaret, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1896-1900 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Cook, James H., 1924 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Jefferson, 1808-1889, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Forbes, Henry Clinton, 1833-1903, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Forrest, Edwin, 1806-1872, 1870 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Gardiner, Francis, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Godwin, William, 1813 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gounod, Charles François, 1818-1893, 1855-1873 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Hall, Newmann, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Hinkel, John W., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Houseman, Laurence, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Howells, William Dean, 1894-1910 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson, Joseph, 1878 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - King, Frank M., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Knowles, James S., 1835 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Landor, Walter Savage, 1775-1864, 1847 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - MacDowell, Edward, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Manna-Zucca, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1914-1929 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Moore, George, 1852-1933, 1916? (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Pape, Eric, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Prescott, Mary N., undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Proctor, Barry Cornwall, 1858 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Quincy, Edmund, 1843 (Box 10, Folder 33)